what else Toby's alright we're gonna
give everybody a little bit of time to
get in here five minutes just like HQ
trivia this is God Scottie mix garrison
your ascots or whatever other stupid
names he has for himself but you know he
does make you miss the guy right you
watch enough HQ trivias with Scott it's
like some Scott home Stockholm Syndrome
you know welcome welcome to our our
product announcement um Vivian right
here that's a new thing team Carl right
teams to Carla you know like the little
gang and the Jake Pollard's come this is
karma CES look at our power look at how
much power we have wow so much power yo
you guys you Scopus let me show you
something so we ran out of power in the
basement so we bought some extension
cords and we ran them from up here to
down there so you can maybe equal go
we'll go take a quick look at them yeah
right
we have power that is right and we have
power because we're not beholden to
agencies like see yeah so I checked it
out this is the bundle of extension
cords that's power man okay um I think
we're gonna switch you to horizontal
yeah we were trippin breakers alright we
got a hundred people in here alright and
they've ready to bring it in and Eddie
Eddie is gonna say a few words about the
product I think two if you want stuff
come to our new stockroom and you see
some of the stuff is censored with
commas that's our internal stock here's
our presentation monitor goes right to
the masses out of my laptop here here's
our current product lineup if you're
unfamiliar with it we have look at that
look at that we have the Panda we have a
Honda giraffe on the left a Toyota
giraffe on the right we have two Yuans
in the back there one of them you can't
tell what one of them 64 gave one of
those 128 two minutes two minutes come
on come on come on three hundreds yeah
when you guys order stuff you know where
it comes from now this is the sauce room
yeah we work hard oh my god that is I'm
doing inventory downstairs and we have
like 200 more down today we have to have
we better have more cuz that's not
enough yeah you guys today guess what's
in this box
brand new come AI hoodies super
comfortable super comfortable only $249
cheaper it's a very cheap price yes
supreme supreme us I'm not actually
going nice entry merchandise you say you
would um yeah this used to be the
headquarters of crypto scams LLC we are
policy went out of business all of
Krypton today is very legitimate yeah
it's all very legitimate okay yeah
cuz we would start too early we would
start to all and everyone would go
through yeah come in here putting up
some real high quality journey in here
yeah so don't mess with me don't mess
around with our stockroom you see the
censorship these are our prices of
existing stuff good $99 pan this we owe
can't show them that one that one no I
know I know I know it's not a blurred
out in that post-it notes by the way I
was watching I sometimes I like watching
periscope - I'm doing my slash I was
doing the shot oh this way yeah come and
I like slash shop alright so I'm like T
comma to you
comma what's poppin everybody welcome to
the come AI product and now it's been
you are not at CES we are not at CES
either they wouldn't pay for my flight
and as you know you know as as as a
member of team combo we like things like
flights pay for so yeah our slogan is
girls riding for the masses and we have
2.7 million miles in our training set
and that is all thanks to you guys out
out Tina karma the best self-driving car
team on the internet better than team
Tesla better than team lame-o better
than team crews I don't even think as a
team I think they got all right yeah so
shout out to you all know about the Eon
this is the Eon is great universal
computing hardware two wheels right here
a whole lot of emails over there will be
by when they ship out so today we're
announcing some midnight black
just let me just wipe this down it
really is it really is beautiful
I so we start with all black everything
and we finish with all black everything
black anodized heatsink guys how hot
does that does that look right midnight
black yawns the the phone is black the
screws are black we pay attention to
detail they are all black everything
maybe maybe we'll even make a custom
exclusive black theme for midnight now
we're not going that far but but you can
buy your midnight black Eon for 829
dollars they're all 128 gig to shop that
comedy guy that is already live midnight
black eons they are really really that
you you you have one of these in your
car it's a nice addition to your car
midnight black beyond so that did guys
thank you for joining us for therefore
the product announced no I would i do
that let's go fees you're saving I was
like oh it's so weird I that's it I mean
we just a midnight blanky on this all
we're doing kid yeah no you guys know
about the Panda right pen is the nicest
universal car on her face ever
we should got a lot of canvas a lot
we're actually seriously almost out of
hand so I sure have a canister left is a
lot guys we started out with 2000 and as
more than one tooth out of it I give it
2200 and that's that's what's left but
never fear we're getting a new order of
10,000 pandas we're really going to try
to make the Panda a five-star experience
there's we want to eventually be on
Amazon Prime and the be on Amazon Prime
you really have to offer five-star
experience this starts from the software
all the way down to the hardware all the
way down to knowing whether your car is
supported or not before you buy a panda
know
what you can get access to automatic
fingerprinting much is your pairing
process this is all the stuff we need to
provide a five-star and experience and
one of the things that we're doing that
we're announcing today is the brand-new
injection molded panda case check it out
so it's actually slightly smaller I
didn't even know this was possible but
you know we've we got we got great
people working for us
putting pandas in injection molded cases
these things look real nice in 10,000 of
these they're gonna come in a really
cute little box um so if you buy a panda
from here on out you're getting a panda
in an injection-molded case so we just
go changing the case we're changing the
color these are exciting yes but you
know 61 people are product announcements
you ready you ready hey
Skokie's want to see you it is alive any
kind of yet but have a seat maybe maybe
you can you can pull it out
Oh kind of nice yeah yeah gray laptop so
we got uh red lights and stop signs so
you know team comma you're all on with
team comma we are probably unless Tesla
comes out of nowhere gonna ship the
first aftermarket system capable of
doing red lights and stop signs now as
you know we've talked about needing one
more piece of hardware to do it it's not
a very big piece of hardware it's
definitely capable on a neon it's been
referred to as the pigeon yeah although
that that's not the final name team
comma kiddo back to comma 2 comma can
call the shoutout please go yeah we'd
like to stop sense when we made possible
with the great
the great pan but the case is still a
bit in progress still early prototype
the case is looking fine but yeah it's
gray it's a panda but we got rid of
Wi-Fi and replaced it with a high
precision GPS that's this SMA connector
you see here here's what it looks like
on the inside so we're using a u-blox
module George posted a tweeted a pic of
that yeah so that little antenna
connector sticks out and then you screw
in your external antenna we'd have a
nice mount for this that'll stick to
your windshield yeah yeah pretty much it
so this be compatible with with Aeons
just plug in your your gray Panda
instead of your white panda yeah screw
this guy in here so when you connect to
your panda to Yuri on Wi-Fi shuts off
already talk about the difference
between a pendant and everywhere else
sure so yeah we got so like I suppose
saying when you plug in your panda into
your beyond the Wi-Fi model gonna shut
off plus we have the USB connection so
you weren't using that module also we
replaced it with a GPS mode that's the
big difference one as GPS
so you just got your gray panda here
instead of a white panda and it adds
this GPS now open pilot is still going
to totally work with white pandas always
it's all gonna work with white canvas
but if you really want that super high
precision you know the kind of precision
we need for red lights and stop signs
you're gonna want a great panel
yeah need that external GPS to get
better reception drop into the placement
how much are they going for well we got
there these these are the GPS in here is
so good radio knows your antenna makes a
huge difference you know and you mount
them in such a way that it's this is
like parallel to the ground so you're
not gonna get multipath off of the
ground what we can also do with this
module that we can't do with the other
one is carrier phase and Doppler shifts
by getting Doppler shifts so you guys
know the effect like you hear an aerial
and siren and it's like high-pitched
when it comes and low pitch when it goes
you can use that same effect with
satellites to determine your speed super
precisely so that's something that's a
great panda will enable these new
carrier fairs our target for the end of
the year combining our open-source HD
maps gray pandas and beyond so just what
you see here will have you localized
with ten centimeters of accuracy well
know where you are within ten
centimeters anywhere in the world and
we'll be able to use this to improve the
driving experience and obviously do stop
signs in red lights
so how do you get a great Panda yeah
high precision GPS plus all wiring panda
function so you have like it has the
same three cat bus as tool in buses GM
land yeah
hey yep for sale right now let's shop
back onto the I shop comma dot a I maybe
we'll just do that not that I slash shop
just
know it's just for one person but we're
not gonna do it whatever they should do
it we should chant we should just live
shop / alright so much shopping with REI
we're trying to come with a jingle no no
pause it go--pause
no girl is not live yet it is life in
his life
oh no no shop to come no comment that I
asked last shop is not live but the
grape and animal is live you can do a
break you can do a drop down right on
the panda for $199 you can get yourself
a great handout shipping in for 12 weeks
you know there's still a few uh there's
a few things to work yeah a few things
now but they do work really they do work
or a great band together way if you're
one of the top five Eon users in January
by miles by five minutes we don't care
if using shipper plus or open pilot five
minutes where you're moving no cheating
minutes the top IBM users will be mailed
free of charge a great Canada prototype
that will let us gather statistics on
how well these things are working in the
field to make sure all and paying
customers get the highest quality
they'll kind of be ready great pandas
will eventually shut the rest see gray
panda so yeah the reason it's not the
pigeon the reason we didn't name it the
pigeon the pigeon is a code name is
because some people are gonna be like oh
I need a panda and a pigeon
no you just need a great panda or white
panda open pilot you continue to work
with white pandas and
for shipper only works with white hands
shipper does not work with greg pass
vanilla gorilla order place amazing what
if you open order for white pan at the
want gray yeah yeah seven email to
support at calm down AI with your order
number and then we'll go ahead and do
the exchange um if you don't know though
you probably want to white panda unless
you're sure you want a gray panda and
does it come with the antenna it does
come with you
absolutely that's kind of why the price
is so high yeah I'm not sure it's gonna
be this antenna but full disclosure
these antennas cost us like forty five
bucks and it's gonna be some kind of
mounting solution that's a solution do
moderators get one why would you want a
white panda a very great one oh because
it is Wi-Fi Kobe goes to high Wall
Street yeah
white pandas are kind of gonna be there
the mainstream of pandas if you want to
live on the edge great that maverick
panda well it comes supporting we're not
nice and red stop signs and red lights
probably not but it will support a
better localization experience by the
time you share what about me or users
I'm gonna find young very great pandas
are not not to learn any yes you know
are the future guys are the future yes
or no it is time for questions and if
anyone from the press is out there
watching follow-up phone call we get any
questions answered except for BAM
questions you'll know the band questions
don't ask me when your Fiats gonna be
supportive and definitely don't ask me
when your supers could it be supportive
yet so accurate do you need to make sure
your antennas centered on the card so no
the last bit of precision is done by the
camera so you need to make sure your
aeon camera is centered on the car but
your antenna centered is probably better
but I would
um what does better localization mean to
the user right now right now really just
always nice we were right now it's
better ways buyouts yeah ways will be
off sometimes right because your phone
GPS gets crappy we can free inject those
GPS signal into it if you realize order
a great panda now by the time it arrives
it should improve your driving
experience so thing that we can do we
found problem during the road trip of
the wind like the wind would blow the
car and it would take a long time for
our thing to learn that the wind was
blowing the car humans realize this
right away because humans have a very
good localization system how do you know
the winds blow in your car or I feel it
pushing my car look my cars going this
way you know to correct the system
that's doing this right now is fairly
weak um we're gonna start tying the
localizer in with that system so if you
have a great panda your like steering
angle offset learning will be improved
by the time great hand of USD folks
sorry no card sorry please end up being
pushed in car entertainment systems you
know it just runs that you're young you
wouldn't want it to be pushed your car
infotainment system because those things
that oh well the dimensions be very
similar to the white panda there are
they yeah it's exactly the same except
for the antenna sticking out why do bed
late for choir GPS um so the hard thing
that red lights isn't detecting whether
they're right early hey we get we get
emails from people or slack a certain
people were like look man this kid built
a red light detector in five minutes
look how come you can't ship this well
the hard part about red lights
isn't detecting the light it's knowing
where to stop knowing given this light
where exactly do I need to stop the car
and that's what requires high precision
immobilization also knowing does this
light apply to me right it's really easy
to detect humans messes up - oh it was
weird corner intersections yeah daddy
mystery really easy to detect
is there a stop sign in the image really
hard to detect okay
even that that stop signs they are where
should I stop you know some cities will
have a stop sign on the other side
pointing towards you yeah so oh and how
we gonna get this data like coloring
style live comic style but live on the
Mac you'll be able to edit your route
and be like here's a red light here's a
stop sign
let's just let's just show this go like
what's the real difference between a
midnight black no 128k it's midnight
black is black it's prettier but it does
only come in 128k it does yeah this is
this is this is the premium yeah and the
side of the oneplus is black yeah
no more gunmetal yeah no we're gonna we
can't be too mean to that's really no
that's really that yeah yeah come on man
how do you know why you dumped in that
block yeah now you know but you still
get a white cable so we got some black
cable should we show you yeah
are they back in stock yeah they're back
okay if they're back in find enough
black young boy blue black cables yeah
these are these will ship out in a week
yeah all next week next Wednesday we
should sign up this Wednesday
pandas are a little bit delayed they
shouldn't be too much yeah what time is
it it's a three 18:39 midnight black no
swag no no snack but we'll show you us
that we already have
[Music]
the hood apocalypse I don't know some
people accuse me according hoodies in my
room very many of the older ones
reported quite a few what do you mean oh
my god can I show them yeah you guys
look at how red light stops oh come on
that's so cool alright I got a slightly
different profile you guys will be happy
with these alright everybody that is the
periscope thank you for joining us for
product announcement today quick recap
we got the midnight black yon midnight
black and we have the I spelt it with an
A is that controversial yeah why
how does Sasha grasp on you with any
that's a great album what about a whoa
whoa I think that Shopify doesn't
support that um so yeah here here's a
gray panda right here plugged into a
honda giraffe you can see that gps
antenna on the other side there sasha is
an e midnight is usually dark but it's
grey in the US with an a thank you Alex
great yeah yeah I'm not dwell it British
to you gray eagle alright thank you for
joining us uh yeah common Teemo team
common team come we're gonna do it we're
gonna make a thing